A Guide to the Danville (Va.) Civil Rights Case Files, 1963-1973
Library of Virginia
- Virginia Supreme Court of Appeals (Reel 2329)
  Consists of decisions handed down from October 1965-December 1972. Primarily includes writs of errors and supersedeases.
  - Folder List:
  - Decisions, Doyle J. Thomas, et al, October 1965
  - Decisions, Lillie Echols Hubbard, October 1965 - January 1967
  - Decisions, March - October 1967
  - Decisions, March - June 1968
  - Decisions, June - November 1970
  - Decisions, January 1971, December 1972
  - Decisions, Lawrence George Campbell, et al. vs. City of Danville December 1972
- Dictabelts (38099-1 - 38099-39)
  Comprises soundrecordings from 130 dictabelts, which contain a full apprising of the Danville Civil Rights Demonstrations Corporation Court Cases. Includes witnesses' testimony, defense attorney's motions and arguments, Commonwealth and Danville City attorney's arguments, rulings and sentences of Judge Archibald M. Aiken, witness and recorder oaths, and the calling of the court docket. The court heard cases from 13 December to 23 December 1966 and from 7 February to 21 February and 6 April 1967. Also contained herein is the recording of the 9 February 1973 Corporation Court hearing concerning the defense motion to suspend the sentences for those defendants whose sentences had been upheld on appeal by the Supreme Court of Appeals. These dictabelts also included inserts containing written summaries of their audio contents and in most cases copies of the original court docket. A project was completed by Dictaphone Corporation to record and transfer the audio contents and the inserts of these dictabelts onto compact disc. Below is an inventory of the dictabelts.
  - Irvin Christopher Bethel, et. als., 13-14 December 1966 (Belts 1-15), Total time: 5 hours, 31 minutes, 58 seconds (38099-1 and 38099-2)
    - Recording file 2k204-001 13 December 1966, Defendants roll call/ Attorneys' arguments in Judge's chambers in re: consolidating cases/ [27:14] (38099-1)
    - Recording file 2k204-002 13 December 1966, Attorneys' arguments in Judge's chambers in re: consolidating cases (continued)/ Reading of Judge's injunction issued 6 June 1963/ Defendants' pleas/ [27:56] (38099-1)
    - Recording file 2k204-003 13 December 1966, Eugene G. McCain (chief of police) testimony/ [29:59] (38099-1)
    - Recording file 2k204-004 13 December 1966, Charles Wade Graff (police officer and photographer) testimony/ T. Neil Morris (police officer) testimony/ [29:59] (38099-1)
    - Recording file 2k204-005 13 December 1966, L. P. Rigney (police officer) testimony/ Curtis H. Royster (police officer) testimony/ W. L. Buettner (police officer) testimony/ Curtis H. Royster recall testimony/ Adjournment/ Reconvene/ T. C. Tatterhorn (police officer) testimony/ R. W. Brumfield (police officer) testimony/ [30:00] (38099-1)
    - Recording file 2k204-006 13 December 1966, W. L. Sheffield (police officer) testimony/ C. L. Fuller (police officer) testimony/ R. A. Walker (police officer) testimony/ D. E. Nostrand (police officer) testimony/ B. C. Enyard (police officer) testimony/ John M. Bailey (police officer) testimony/ [27:01] (38099-1)
    - Recording file 2k204-007 13 December 1966, John M. Bailey testimony (continued)/ Unidentified (police officer) testimony/ T. W. Evans (police officer) testimony/ Sutaliff (police officer) testimony/ Unidentified (police officer) testimony/ L. P. Rigney (police officer) testimony/ [26:48] (38099-1)
    - Recording file 2k204-008 13 December 1966, Ernest Howard Smith (demonstrator) testimony/ Defense attorneys' motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ Adjournment and weather report/ [25:33] (38099-1)
    - Recording file 2k204-009 14 December 1966, Convene and roll call/ Approach bench - discussion/ Charles Wade Graff (police officer and photographer) testimony/ Juby E. Towler (chief of police detectives) testimony/ [30:00] (38099-2)
    - Recording file 2k204-010 14 December 1966, Juby E. Towler testimony (continued)/ City attorney argument against defense motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ Defense attorney re-argues motion to strike evidence/ [30:00] (38099-2)
    - Recording file 2k204-011 14 December 1966, Defense attorney re-argues motion to strike evidence (continued)/ Judge's ruling on motion (denied)/ Adjournment/ Reconvene/ Defense motion to remove some defendant's names from case docket/ [29:04] (38099-2)
    - Recording file 2k204-012 14 December 1966, Defense attorney motion to strike evidence and witness testimony (continued)/ Judge's ruling on motion (denied)/ James Edward Whipple (demonstrator) testimony/ [10:19] (38099-2)
    - Recording file 2k204-013 14 December 1966, James Edward Whipple testimony (continued)/ W. L. Buettner recall testimony/ Unidentified (police officer) recall testimony/ Prosecution rests/ Defense closing/ [28:41] (38099-2)
    - Recording file 2k204-014 14 December 1966, Defense closing (continued)/ Prosecution closing/ Judge's ruling and sentences/ [29:53] (38099-2)
    - Recording file 2k204-015 14 December 1966, Attorneys' arguments in Judge's chambers in re: bond hearing for absentee defendants/ Adjournment/ [9:15] (38099-2)
  - Sylvester Burrell, et. als. 15 December 1966 (Belts 1-12), Total time: 5 hours, 19 minutes, 20 seconds (38099-3, 38099-4, 38099-4a)
    - Recording file 2k204-016 15 December 1966, Convene/ Recorder sworn/ Defendants roll call/ Cases consolidated/ Eugene G. McCain (chief of police) testimony/ [29:53] (38099-3)
    - Recording file 2k204-017 15 December 1966, Eugene G. McCain testimony (continued)/ [30:01] (38099-3)
    - Recording file 2k204-018 15 December 1966, Eugene G. McCain testimony (continued)/ Recess/ Reconvene/ Eugene G. McCain testimony (continued)/ [29:28] (38099-3)
    - Recording file 2k204-019 15 December 1966, Eugene G. McCain testimony (continued)/ [30:00] (38099-3)
    - Recording file 2k204-020 15 December 1966, T. Neil Morris (police officer) testimony/ Lunch recess/ Reconvene/ T. Neil Morris testimony (continued)/ Charles Wade Graff (police officer and photographer) testimony/ [29:59] (38099-3)
    - Recording file 2k204-021 15 December 1966, Charles Wade Graff testimony (continued)/ Attorneys' arguments in Judge's chambers in re: photographs and time of their development/ Charles Wade Graff testimony (continued)/ Juby E. Towler (chief of police detectives) testimony/ [29:44] (38099-4)
    - Recording file 2k204-022 15 December 1966, Juby E. Towler testimony (continued)/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ Re-re-direct/ Re-re-cross/ Ralph Wilkerson (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ Charles Wade Graff recall testimony/ Recess/ Reconvene/ B. C. Elliott Jr. (police officer) testimony/ [29:37] (38099-4)
    - Recording file 2k204-023 15 December 1966, B. C. Elliott Jr. testimony (continued) testimony/ Prosecution and Defense rests/ Defense motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ Judge's ruling on motion (denied)/ Defense motion to strike because arrest did not occur at time of violation/ Judge's ruling on motion (denied)/ Recess/ Reconvene/ Wade Thompson (demonstrator) testimony/ [29:34] (38099-4)
    - Recording file 2k204-024 15 December 1966, Wade Thompson testimony (continued)/ Harvey Smith (demonstrator) testimony/ Paul Price (demonstrator) testimony/ Stuart Walter Mayo (demonstrator) testimony/ [29:36] (38099-4)
    - Recording file 2k204-025 15 December 1966, Otha Frank Lumpkin (demonstrator) testimony/ Adjournment/ [11:17] (38099-4)
    - Recording file Track 1 16 December 1966, Reconvene/ Defense renews motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ Judge's ruling on motion (overruled)/ Defense motion to dismiss against 5 defendants because prosecution has not proven a case/ Commonwealth argument against motion/ Judge's ruling on motion (overruled)/ Prosecution opening argument/ Defense closing argument/ Judge questions Defense attorneys/ Prosecution closing argument/ Judge's ruling and sentences/ [28:19] (38099-4a)
    - Recording file Track 2 16 December 1966, Judge's ruling and sentences (continued: unclear, distorted sound)/ Defense motion to suspend sentences pending appeal/ [11:49] (38099-4a)
  - James Edward Whipple 16 December 1966 (Belt 1), Total time: 3 minutes, 43 seconds (38099-5)
    - Recording file 2k204-026 16 December 1966, Prosecution motion for a bench warrant to be issued for the arrest of James Edward Whipple on a charge of perjury/ Judge's ruling on motion (granted)/ [3:43] (38099-5)
  - Joseph Bowe, et. als. 16 and 19 December 1966 (Belts 1-10), Total time: 4 hours, 37 minutes, 52 seconds (38099-6, 38099-7 and 38099-8)
    - Recording file 2k204-072 16 December 1966, Recorder sworn/ Cases consolidated/ Defendants roll call/ Defendants' pleas/ [27:22] (38099-6)
    - Recording file 2k204-073 16 December 1966, Walter Link (demonstrator) guilty plea/ Judge's sentence/ Adjournment/ Reconvene/ Stipulate injunction become part of the record/ Defendants' pleas/ T. Neil Morris (police officer) testimony/ [29:00] (38099-6)
    - Recording file 2k204-074 16 December 1966, T. Neil Morris testimony (continued)/ Charles Wade Graff (police officer and photographer) testimony/ B. C. Elliott Jr. (police officer) testimony/ William G. Doss (police officer) testimony/ [28:17] (38099-6)
    - Recording file 2k204-075 16 December 1966, William G. Doss testimony (continued)/ Eugene G. McCain (chief of police) testimony/ [28:24] (38099-7)
    - Recording file 2k204-076 16 December 1966, Eugene G. McCain testimony (continued)/ Recess and adjournment until Monday, 19 December/ [16:56] (38099-7)
    - Recording file 2k204-027 19 December 1966, Reconvene/ W. L. Sheffield (police officer) testimony/ [29:48] (38099-8)
    - Recording file 2k204-028 19 December 1966, P. L. Rowland (police officer) testimony/ T. C. Talley (police officer) testimony/ Recess/ Reconvene/ Eugene G. McCain recall testimony/ [29:37] (38099-8)
    - Recording file 2k204-029 19 December 1966, Eugene G. McCain recall testimony (continued)/ Prosecution rests/ City motion to dismiss cases against Joseph Bowe, Reverend Doyle J. Thomas, and Paul Wade Jr./ Judge grants and dismisses cases/ Defense motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ Judge's ruling on motion (denied)/ B. C. Elliott recall testimony/ Recess/ Reconvene/ Percy Randolph Williams (demonstrator) testimony/ [29:26] (38099-8)
    - Recording file 2k204-030 19 December 1966, Percy Randolph Williams testimony (continued)/ Thomas F. Tucker (Danville Clerk of Court) testimony/ Defense rests/ Defense motion to show cause/ Defense motion to quash capias/ [29:30] (38099-8)
    - Recording file 2k204-031 19 December 1966, Defense motion to quash capias (continued)/ City argument and rebuttal against motion/ Judge's ruling on motion (overruled)/ Defense renews motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ Judge's ruling on motion (overruled)/ Defense motions (various)/ Judge's ruling on motions (overruled)/ Judge's ruling and sentences/ Defense motion to suspend sentences pending appeal/ [29:30] (38099-8)
  - Ruth L. Harvey 20 December 1966 (Belt 1), Total time: 2 minutes, 16 seconds (38099-9)
    - Recording file 2k204-077 20 December 1966, Ruth L. Harvey held in contempt of court for misleading court on location of Leonard Winston Holt (demonstrator/defendant)/ Judge fines Harvey $25/ [2:16] (38099-9)
  - Everett Bruce Jr., et. als. 20 December 1966 (Belts 1-5), Total time: 1 hour, 55 minutes, 4 seconds (38099-10)
    - Recording file 2k204-078 20 December 1966, Convene/ Recorder sworn/ Docket set/ Reverend L. W. Chase statement (found guilty in absence on 19 December 1966)/ Judge's ruling and sentence for Chase/ Defense motion to suspend pending appeal/ Recess/ Reconvene/ [28:17] (38099-10)
    - Recording file 2k204-079 20 December 1966, /Defendants roll call/ Bonds forfeited for those defendants who are absent/ Leonard Winston Holt (demonstrator) case in absentia/ [28:00] (38099-10)
    - Recording file 2k204-080 20 December 1966, Hector Womack (bondsman for Leonard Winston Holt) testimony as to location of Holt/ Adjournment/ [11:31] (38099-10)
    - Recording file 2k204-081 20 December 1966, Leonard Winston Holt bond forfeited/ Judge's ruling and sentence of Holt/ Defense motion to suspend sentence pending appeal/ Recess/ Thomas Mabin (demonstrator) testimony/ Betty H. Dallas (juvenile probation officer) testimony/ Thomas Mabin case dismissed/ Judge's ruling and sentences remaining defendants/ [28:08] (38099-10)
    - Recording file 2k204-082 20 December 1966, Judge's ruling and sentences (continued)/ [19:07] (38099-10)
  - Foss, Zelner and Donaldson (contempt cases for being absent) 23 December 1966 (Belts 1-3), Total time: 1 hour, 13 minutes, 16 seconds (38099-11)
    - Recording file 2k204-083 23 December 1966, Recorder sworn/ Defendants roll call/ Witnesses sworn/ John Robert Zelner (demonstrator) testimony/ Defense argument/ [28:37] (38099-11)
    - Recording file 2k204-084 23 December 1966, Prosecution argument/ Judge's ruling and sentence/ Motion to suspend sentence pending appeal/ Daniel Aaron Foss (demonstrator) testimony/ Defense argument/ Judge's ruling and sentence/ [26:57] (38099-11)
    - Recording file 2k204-085 23 December 1966, Ivanhoe Gaylord Donaldson (demonstrator) testimony/ Defense argument/ Prosecution argument/ Judge's ruling and sentence/ Motion to suspend sentence pending appeal/ [17:41] (38099-11)
  - Setting the court docket 7 February 1967 (Belts 1-5), Total time: 1 hour, 34 minutes, 51 seconds (38099-12)
    - Recording file 2k204-086 7 February 1967, Recorder sworn/ Defense and Prosecution argument and discussion in re: injunction/ 9 February 1967 Docket set and announced/ [26:23] (38099-12)
    - Recording file 2k204-087 7 February 1967, 10 February 1967 docket set (24 demonstrators arrested behind Police Department on 11 July 1963)/ 10 February 1967 docket set (continued: 12 demonstrators arrested at Belk-Leggett Department Store on 11 July 1963)/ 10 February 1967 docket set (continued: 3 demonstrators arrested at Municipal Building on 11 July 1963)/ 13 February 1967 docket set (15 demonstrators arrested at Municipal Building on 11 July 1963)/ 13 February 1967 docket set (continued: demonstrators arrested at Patton and Union Streets on 12 July 1963)/ 14 February 1967 docket set (demonstrators arrested at Belk-Leggett Department Store on 12 July 1963)/ 14 February 1967 docket set (continued: demonstrators arrested at Patton and Union Streets on 12 July 1963)/ [27:09] (38099-12)
    - Recording file 2k204-088 7 February 1967, 14 February 1967 docket set (continued: demonstrators arrested at Belk-Leggett Department Store and Raylass Department Store on 13 July 1963)/ 14 February 1967 docket set (continued: demonstrators arrested at Country Club Drive on 14 July 1963)/ 15 February 1967 docket set (demonstrators arrested at Main and Crawford Streets on 15 July 1963)/ 16 February 1967 docket set (81 demonstrators arrested at Main and Union Streets on 28 July 1963)/ 16 February 1967 docket set (continued: 4 demonstrators arrested at Main Street Bridge on 6 August 1963)/ 20 February 1967 docket set (9 demonstrators arrested at Union Street on 8 August 1963)/ 20 February 1967 docket set (continued: demonstrators arrested at Main and Union Streets on 27 August 1963)/ [27:36] (38099-12)
    - Recording file 2k204-089 7 February 1967, 20 February 1967 docket set (continued: demonstrators arrested at Main and Union Streets on 29 August 1963)/ 14 February 1967 docket omissions added/ Adjournment until Thursday/ [9:40] (38099-12)
    - Recording file 2k204-090 7 February 1967, Discussion in Judge's chambers (unclear, difficult to hear)/ [4:01] (38099-12)
  - Clarence Lewis Bowe, et. als. 9 February 1967 (Belts 1-7), Total time: 2 hours, 43 minutes, 35 seconds (38099-13 and 38099-14)
    - Recording file 2k204-091 9 February 1967, Recorder sworn/ Defendants roll call (3 defendants tried in absentia)/ Witnesses sworn/ Defense motion to quash capias/ Defense motion for bill of particulars/ Judge's ruling on motions (overruled)/ Commonwealth attorney notes exception to bill of particulars/ Norman H. Boswell (captain of police) testimony/ [25:32] (38099-13)
    - Recording file 2k204-092 9 February 1967, Norman H. Boswell testimony (continued)/ Judge questions witness/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ Leon Townsend (Danville Register-Bee photographer) testimony/ Re-direct/ [24:59] (38099-13)
    - Recording file 2k204-093 9 February 1967, Leon Townsend testimony (continued)/ Eugene G. McCain (chief of police) testimony/ B. C. Elliott Jr. (police officer) testimony/ [28:36] (38099-13)
    - Recording file 2k204-094 9 February 1967, B. C. Elliott Jr. testimony (continued)/ Recess/ Reconvene/ B. C. Elliott Jr. testimony (continued)/ William G. Doss (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ [29:24] (38099-13)
    - Recording file 2k204-095 9 February 1967, C. L. Fuller (police officer) testimony/ P. L. Rowland (police officer) testimony/ Ralph Wilkinson (police officer) testimony/ [26:38] (38099-14)
    - Recording file 2k204-096 9 February 1967, Ralph Wilkinson testimony (continued)/ Prosecution rests/ Defense motion/ Judge's ruling on motion (overruled)/ Defense motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ Prosecution argument against motion/ Judge's ruling on motion (overruled)/ Defense rests/ Closing arguments/ Judge's ruling and sentences/ Defense motion to suspend sentences pending appeal/ [28:11] (38099-14)
    - Recording file 2k204-097 9 February 1967, [No intelligible content] [0:13] (38099-14)
  - James Vondell Bruce, et. als. 10 and 15 February 1967 (Belts 1-8), Total time: 3 hours, 16 minutes, 2 seconds (38099-15, 38099-16 and 38099-17)
    - Recording file 2k204-098 10 February 1967, Recorder sworn/ Docket called/ Witnesses sworn/ Defense motion to quash capias/ Judge's ruling on motion (overruled)/ Eugene G. McCain (chief of police) testimony/ [29:39] (38099-15)
    - Recording file 2k204-099 10 February 1967, Eugene G. McCain testimony (continued)/ Judge questions witness/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ T. G. Faulkner (police officer) testimony/ E. L. Holley (police officer) testimony/ [26:23] (38099-15)
    - Recording file 2k204-100 10 February 1967, E. L. Holley testimony (continued)/ Recess/ Reconvene/ E. L. Holley testimony (continued)/ Norman H. Boswell (captain of police) testimony/ L. P. Rigney (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ C. B. Scearce (police officer) testimony/ [26:51] (38099-15)
    - Recording file 2k204-101 10 February 1967, C. B. Scearce testimony (continued)/ J. B. Martin Jr. (police officer) testimony/ W. L. Buettner (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ John M. Bailey (police officer) testimony/ Norman H. Boswell recall testimony/ [27:37] (38099-16)
    - Recording file 2k204-102 10 February 1967, Norman H. Boswell recall testimony (continued)/ H. R. Chaney (police officer) testimony/ J. C. Lewis (police officer) testimony/ Prosecution rests/ Defense motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ Judge's ruling on motion (overruled)/ Defense motions renewed/ Judge's ruling on renewed motions (overruled)/ Charles Wade Graff (police officer and photographer) testimony/ Juby E. Towler (captain of police) testimony/ Defense rests/ Prosecution waives opening remarks/ Defense closing argument/ [26:34] (38099-16)
    - Recording file 2k204-103 10 February 1967, Defense closing argument (continued)/ Prosecution closing remarks/ Judge's ruling and sentences/ Defense motion to suspend sentences pending appeal/ [19:45] (38099-16)
    - Recording file 2k204-104 15 February 1967, Recorder sworn/ Witnesses sworn/ T. G. Faulkner (police officer) testimony/ Defense motion in re: double jeopardy/ Judge's ruling on motion (denied)/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ Re-re-direct/ James L. Miller (police officer) testimony/ [28:36] (38099-17)
    - Recording file 2k204-105 15 February 1967, James L. Miller testimony (continued)/ Walter Riddle testimony/ Prosecution rests/ Defense renews motion in re: double jeopardy/ Defense rests/ Judge's ruling and sentences/ Defense motion to suspend sentences pending appeal/ [10:35] (38099-17)
  - William Burrell Canada, et. als. 13 February 1967 (Belts 1-3), Total time: 1 hour, 12 minutes, 2 seconds (38099-18)
    - Recording file 2k204-106 13 February 1967, Recorder sworn/ Witnesses sworn/ Defense motions renewed/ Judge's ruling on motions (overruled)/ Lonnie Riddle (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ J. W. Martin (police officer) testimony/ [28:33] (38099-18)
    - Recording file 2k204-107 13 February 1967, J. W. Martin testimony (continued)/ L. P. Rigney (police officer) testimony/ W. L. Buettner (police officer) testimony/ C. B. Scearce (police officer) testimony/ Prosecution rests/ Defense motions renewed/ Prosecution arguments against defense motions/ [28:18] (38099-18)
    - Recording file 2k204-108 13 February 1967, Prosecution argument against defense motions (continued)/ Judge's ruling on motions (overruled)/ Defense rests/ Judge's ruling and sentences/ [15:10] (38099-18)
  - Herman Joseph Chappelle, et. als. 13 February 1967 (Belt 1), Total time: 11 minutes, 32 seconds (38099-19)
    - Recording file 2k204-109 13 February 1967, Recorder sworn/ Cases consolidated/ Witnesses sworn/ Eugene G. McCain (chief of police) testimony/ Nolle pros'd (all 10 defendants' cases dismissed)/ [11:32] (38099-19)
  - Elnora Elizabeth Chase, et. als. 13 February 1967 (Belts 1-5), Total time: 1 hour, 51 minutes, 13 seconds (38099-20)
    - Recording file 2k204-119 13 February 1967, Nolle pros'd (continued: from previous trial of Herman Joseph Chappelle, et. als.)/ Recorder sworn/ Docket called/ Cases consolidated/ Eugene G. McCain (chief of police) testimony/ Recess/ [24:30] (38099-20)
    - Recording file 2k204-120 13 February 1967, Reconvene/ Eugene G. McCain testimony (continued)/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ C. E. Earles (police officer) testimony/ T. C. Talley (police officer) testimony/ [26:46] (38099-20)
    - Recording file 2k204-121 13 February 1967, T. C. Talley testimony (continued)/ R. W. Brumfield (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ Re-cross/ Roy Larsen (police officer) testimony/ Curtis H. Royster (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ P. L. Barber (police officer) testimony/ E. L. Carter (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ [27:07] (38099-20)
    - Recording file 2k204-122 13 February 1967, D. L. Haley (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ Prosecution rests/ Defense motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ Judge's ruling on motion (overruled)/ Recess/ Reconvene/ Defense rests/ Judge's ruling and sentences/ [27:33] (38099-20)
    - Recording file 2k204-123 13 February 1967, Judge's ruling and sentences (continued)/ Defense motion to suspend sentences pending appeal/ [5:14] (38099-20)
  - David Adams, et. als. 14 February 1967 (Belts 1-6), Total time: 2 hours, 10 minutes, 4 seconds (38099-21 and 38099-22)
    - Recording file 2k204-110 13 February 1967, Recorder sworn/ Cases consolidated/ Defense motions/ P. L. Rowland (police officer) testimony/ C. L. Fuller (police officer) testimony/ [27:49] (38099-21)
    - Recording file 2k204-111 14 February 1967, C. L. Fuller testimony (continued)/ Jackson H. Brown (police officer) testimony/ Re-direct/ Curtis H. Royster (police officer) testimony/ Thomas W. Evans (police officer) testimony/ Prosecution rests/ Defense motion to strike evidence and witness testimony/ [29:59] (38099-21)
    - Recording file 2k204-112 14 February 1967, Defense motion to strike evidence and witness testimony (continued)/ Edgar Lee Via (demonstrator) testimony/ Ralph McDonald Hairston (demonstrator) testimony/ [29:20] (38099-21)
    - Recording file 2k204-113 14 February 1967, Ralph McDonald Hairston testimony (continued)/ [13:36] (38099-22)